

Mykhailo Peremskyi

JUNIOR MANUAL QA ENGINEER

CONTACT

- 796 865 039
- in mykhailo-peremskyi
- michal.peremskyi@gmail.com
- Wrocław, Poland

SKILLS

- Experience in creating test documentation: checklists, test cases, bug reports
- Knowledge of testing types and test design techniques
- Understanding the role of testing in software development
- Understanding of the SDLC/STLC/BLC
- Understanding of Agile frameworks (Scrum, Kanban)
- Practice of working with DevTools (JSON, XML)
- Knowledge and practice with JIRA
- Experience in WEB and mobile testing
- Knowledge of a client-server model (HTTP(s), REST, SOAP)
- Practical experience with databases, SQL (SQLite), API testing (Postman), HTML5 and CSS3, JavaScript
- Basic experience with GIT and command line

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Polish Proficiency
- Russian Fluent
- Ukrainian Native

OBJECTIVE

Responsible and motivated HR Admin Specialist with 2+ years of experience wants to transition to an Manual QA Engineer. I am ready to apply my attention to detail, time management, organizational and relationship-building skills. I will using advanced knowledge to provide best quality of product, build good relationships and support team spirit.

EXPERIENCE

Manual QA Engineer (non-commercial experience) MasterDynamix

September 2022 — October 2022

- Interaction with the team
- Tested the functionality of the program adding a new user
- Compiled test cases, applied test design techniques equivalent class, and boundary values
- Wrote bug reports in the Jira

HR Admin Specialist

Sungdo Eng Poland Sp. z o .o.

January 2021 — Present

- Managing the process of hiring selected candidates
- Personnel service for more than 300 employees
- Carry out the process of hiring foreigners, taking into account all forms of legal residence and work in Poland
- Managing the company's finances in terms of payroll and expenses

Specialist for legalization of stay and work of foreigners **EWIGOL Consulting** Sp. z o .o.

June 2020 — December 2020

- Monitoring the status of administrative proceedings with more than 150 clients
- Contact with administrative authorities regarding procedures in matters of legalization of work and residence of foreigners
- Preparation and completion of necessary documents

CERTIFICATES

- Fullstack Development Qwasar.io
- SQL Sololearn.com
- HTML5/CSS3 Sololearn.com
- Legacy Responsive Web Design Freecodecamp.org

EDUCATION

Manual QA Engineer

TechMission

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

Master of Economic Diplomacy

Maria Curie-Skłodowska University in Lublin

Completion: 2017

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed for the purpose of considering my application for the vacancy advertised